California ephemera collection, 1860-
California Ephemera Collection,
- Pony Express (Box 84)
- Popanoe, Paul (Box 84)
- Port Hueneme, California (Box 285)
- Port of Los Angeles Waterfront Redcar Line. Los Angeles, California. (Box 285)
- Portigal, Steven, 1852 - (Box 84)
  1. CERAMICS
- Post Office (Box 192)
- Pottery
  SEE: Palmdale, Calif.
- Poultry - California (Box 84)
- Power of Place (Box 253)
  Box 197 is an oversize flat box.
- Power, George C., 1852? - 1942 (Box 84)
- Price, Vance J. (Box 84)
- Priester, Alma Dorothy (Box 84)
  1. PRIESTER, ALMA DOROTHY - PORTRAIT
- Private schools - California (Box 176)
- Private schools - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 176, 285)
- Private schools - California - Pasadena (Box 176)
- Private schools - Southern California (Box 196)
- Private Security Services (Box 245)
- Project Angel Food. Los Angeles, California. (Box 222)
- Pruitt, Andrew, 1868 - 1949 (Box 84)
- Psychics (Box 222)
- Publishers and publishing - California (Boxes 85, 199)
- Racial discrimination - California (Box 176)
- Radio industry and trade - Los Angeles (Boxes 86, 255)
  I. Pacifica Foundation. II. K.P.F.K., Los Angeles. III KPFA, Berkeley, Calif.
- Radio stations - California (Boxes 211, 245, 272)
  Box 245 - 2 folders.
- Rafferty, Maxwell Lewis, 1917 - (Box 86)
- Railroads - California (Boxes 86, 245, 285)
- Railroads - California - societies (Box 189)
- Ramona Pageant. Hemet, California (Box 189)
- Ramona, California (Box 189)
- Ramona's marriage place. San Diego, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Camulos. Ventura County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Cucamonga, California (Box 285)
- Rancho El Cortijo (Box 86)
  1. CLARY (WILLIAM W.) RANCH.
- Rancho El Sur. Monterey County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Guajome. San Diego County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Los Amigos. Hondo, California (Box 272)
- Rancho Los Cerritos. Los Angeles County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Mirage, California (Box 272)
- Rancho Paso de Bartolo Viejo (or) San Rafael. Los Angeles County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Rincon. San Bernardino County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho San Antonio. Los Angeles County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres. Los Angeles County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho San Pedro. Los Angeles County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Santa Ana Botanic Garden of Native Plants of California (Box 86)
- Rancho Santa Ana del Chino. San Bernardino County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Santa Anita. Los Angeles County, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Santa Fe, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Santa Margarita y Las Flores. San Diego and Orange Counties, California (Box 86)
- Rancho Topanga Malibu Sequit. Los Angele County, California (Box 87)
  X Rancho Malibu. 1. MALIBU, CALIF. 2. RINDGE ESTATE.
- Ranchos - California (Box 87)
- Rand, Violet (Box 87)
- Randall, Charles Hiram, 1865 - (Box 87)
- Randall, George Archibald, 1888? - 1941 (Box 87)
- Randolph, Epes, 1856 - 1921 (Box 87)
- Rave (Parties) - California (Box 272)
- Reagan, Ronald, 1911 - (Box 176)
- Real estate - California (Box 245)
- Real estate - California - West Los Angeles (Box 222)
- Real estate business - California (Boxes 132, 199)
  Box 132 - 5 folders.
- Real estate business - California - Orange County (Box 176)
- Real estate development - California - San Diego County (Box 176)
- Rebuild LA (Box 191)
- Rechy, John (Box 87)
- Recovery Foundation for Emotionally Disturbed Children. Los Angeles. (Box 87)
- Recycling - California (Boxes 87, 261)
- Recycling (Waste, etc.) - California - Los Angeles (Box 245)
- Red Bluff, California (Tehama County) (Box 87)
- Redding, California (Boxes 87, 285)
- Redlands, California (Boxes 87, 214, 261, 285)
  Box 214 is an oversize box.
- Redlands, California University. (Box 87)
- Redondo Beach, California (Boxes 87, 285)
- Redondo Beach, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Box 286)
- Redondo Hotel. Redondo Beach, California (Box 87)
- Redwood City, California (Box 87)
- Redwood Highway, California (Box 87)
- Redwood National and State Parks (Box 272)
- Reedley, California (Box 245)
- Refuse and Refuse Disposal - California - Los Angeles (Box 87)
- Reid, Hugo, 1811? - 1853 (Box 87)
- Religious literature (Boxes 133, 134, 272)
  Box 134 - 4 folders.
- Religious retreats (Box 286)
- Renaissance Pleasure Faire. Southern California. (Boxes 176, 203)
- Republican Party. California. 1966 - 1967. (Box 176)
- Republican Party. California. To 1966. (Box 176)
- Resorts (Box 87)
- Retirement living - California (Box 192)
- Rexroth, Kenneth, 1905 - (Boxes 87, 251)
- Rhodes, Eugene Manlove, 1869 - 1935 (Box 88)
- Richard M. Nixon Library and Birthplace. Yorba Linda, California (Box 192)
- Richardson Grove, California (Box 286)
- Richardson, Friend William, 1865 - 1943 (Box 88)
  1. RICHARDSON, FRIEND WILLIAM, 1865 - 1943 - PORTRAIT.
- Richmond, California (Box 191)
- Ridgecrest, California (Boxes 245, 273)
- Riley, Bennet, 1787 - 1853 (Box 88)
  1. RILEY, BENNET, 1787 - 1853 - PORTRAIT.
- Rimpau family (Box 88)
- Rindge, Frederick Hastings, 1857 - 1905 (Box 88)
- River rafting - California (Box 286)
- Riverside County, California (Box 245)
- Riverside, California (Box 88)
- Roads - California (Box 88)
- Robyns, Annette (Box 88)
  1. ROBYNS, ANNETTE - PORTRAIT
- Rogers, Will, 1879 - 1935 (Box 88)
- Roller Skating - California (Box 88)
- Rolph, James, 1869 - 1934 (Box 88)
- Romero, Frank (Box 286)
- Roosevelt, James, 1907 - (Box 88)
  1. ROOSEVELT, JAMES, 1907 - - PORTRAIT. 2. ROOSEVELT, ELEANOR (ROOSEVELT), 1884 - 1962-PORTRAIT.
  3. CALIFORNIA - POLITICS AND GOVERNMENT.
- Rosendahl, Bill (Box 273)
- Rosenshine, Albert A., 1882 - (Box 176)
  1. ROSENSHINE, ALBERT A., 1882 - PORTRAIT
- Rosicrucians (Box 89)
- Ross, Ida Hancock (Box 176)
  1. ROSS, IDA HANCOCK - PORTRAIT
- Route 66 (Box 245)
- Rowell, Chester Haryve, 1867 - 1948 (Box 176)
- Rowlands, William (Box 176)
- Royal Way. Los Angeles, California. (Box 273)
- Roybal, Edward R. (Boxes 176, 261)
  Box 261 - Roybal, Edward R. - obituary
- Running Springs, California (Box 222)
- Runyon Canyon (Hollywood, California) (Box 211)
- Russian River (Box 176)
- Sacramento County Historical Society Bulletin (Box 89)
- Sacramento County, California (Box 90)
- Sacramento River (Box 89)
- Sacramento Valley (Box 90)
- Sacramento, California (Boxes 89, 286)
- Saint Helena, California (St. Helena) (Box 246)
- Salinas, California (Box 90)
- Salton Sea, California (Box 90)
- Samuel Johnson Society of Southern California (Box 90)
  1. JOHNSON, SAMUEL, 1709 - 1784.
- San Anselmo, California (Box 177)
  X SAN FRANCISCO THEOLOGICAL SEMINARY. SAN ANSELMO, CALIF.
- San Benito County, California (Box 177)
- San Bernardino County, California (Boxes 177, 253)
- San Bernardino Mountains (Box 177)
- San Bernardino Mountains (California) - Maps (Box 246)
- San Bernardino, California (Box 177)
- San Carlos, California (Box 273)
- San Clemente, California (Boxes 246, 253)
- San Diego County, California (Boxes 92, 247)
- San Diego Eucalyptus Co. (Box 273)
- San Diego Historical Society. San Diego, California (Boxes 212, 247)
- San Diego History Research Center (Box 92)
- San Diego, California (Boxes 91, 92, 251, 286)
  1. ATCHISON, TOPEKA, AND SANTA FE RAILROAD - HISTORY
- San Diego, California - Business cards and promotional material (Box 212)
- San Diego, California - Churches (Box 192)
- San Diego, California - Description and travel (Boxes 212, 247, 273)
  Box 247 - 3 folders.
- San Diego, California - Historic houses, etc. (Box 92)
- San Diego, California - Hotels, taverns, etc. (Boxes 212, 247)
- San Diego, California - Old Town (Box 92)
- San Diego, California - Panama-California Exposition, 1915 - 1916 (Boxes 92, 262)
- San Diego, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Box 247)
- San Diego, California - Transportation (Box 212)
- San Diego, California - Two hundredth anniversary (200th), 1969 (Box 92)
- San Dimas, California (Box 177)
- San Fernando Valley, California (Box 136)
- San Francisco Bay (Box 178)
- San Francisco Bay Area Rapid Transit District (Boxes 246, 286)
- San Francisco, California (Boxes 135, 141, 199, 255)
  Maps filed separately. Box 135 - 3 folders. Box 141 - 4 folders.
- San Francisco, California Alta California. (Box 178)
  Facsimile of vol. 1, no. 260.
- San Francisco, California - Beaches (Box 178)
  1. SAN FRANCISCO - VIEWS (BEACHES)
- San Francisco, California - Buildings (Box 178)
- San Francisco, California - China Town (Box 178)
- San Francisco, California - Churches (Box 178)
- San Francisco, California - Civic Center. (Box 178)
- San Francisco, California - Cliff House. (Box 178)
- San Francisco, California - Description and travel (Boxes 178, 246, 273, 286)
  Box 246 - 2 folders.
- San Francisco, California - Earthquake and fire, 1906 (Boxes 178, 201)
  Box 178 - 3 folders. 1. DISASTERS. 2. EARTHQUAKES. 3. FIRES.
  201 is an oversize folder.
- San Francisco, California - Fire Department. (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Fort Winfield Scott. (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Golden Gate (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Golden Gate Park (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Hotels (Box 93)
  1. SAN FRANCISCO - VIEWS (HOTELS)
- San Francisco, California - Hotels, taverns, etc. (Boxes 246, 286)
- San Francisco, California - Maps and guides (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Oakland Bay Bridge (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Parks (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Boxes 189, 212, 246, 286)
- San Francisco, California - Skyline (Box 93)
- San Francisco, California - Streets (Box 93)
- San Francisquito Canyon, California (Box 94)
- San Gabriel Mountains (Box 94)
- San Gabriel, California (Boxes 94, 286)
- San Jacinto Mountains (Box 94)
- San Jacinto River, California (Box 94)
  1. SAN JACINTO RIVER, CALIF. - VIEWS
- San Joaquin County, California (Box 94)
- San Joaquin Valley, California (Box 189)
- San Jose, California (Boxes 94, 212, 246, 286)
- San Leandro, California (Alameda County) (Box 94)
- San Luis Obispo County, California (Box 189)
- San Luis Obispo, California (Boxes 94, 286)
- San Luis Obispo, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Box 212)
- San Luis Reservoir (California) (Box 286)
- San Marcos Pass, California (Box 94)
  1. SAN MARCOS PASS, CALIF. - VIEWS.
- San Marino, California (Box 94)
- San Mateo County Historical Association (Box 94)
- San Mateo County, California (Boxes 94, 286)
- San Mateo, California (Box 94)
- San Miguel Island, California (Box 95)
- San Nicolas Island (Box 95)
- San Pedro, California (Boxes 95, 213)
- San Rafael, California (Marin County) (Box 95)
- Sanders, Marilyn (Box 95)
- Santa Ana, California (Boxes 95, 286)
- Santa Anita Park. Arcadia, California (Box 95)
- Santa Barbara Historical Society (Box 223)
- Santa Barbara Mission Archive Library (Box 179)
- Santa Barbara, California (Boxes 179, 246, 251, 286)
- Santa Barbara, California - Fiesta Days (Box 196)
  - Old Spanish Days in Santa Barbara: August 18, 19, 20, 1932: official souvenir program., Item No. 1 (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Santa Barbara, California - Hotels, taverns, etc. (Box 189)
- Santa Catalina Island, California (Boxes 95, 223, 253, 286)
  X CATALINA ISLAND. Also shelved oversize.
- Santa Clara County, California (Boxes 96, 246, 286)
- Santa Clara, California (Box 246)
- Santa Cruz County, California (Box 96)
- Santa Cruz, California (Boxes 96, 246)
- Santa Maria Valley, California (Box 96)
  1. SANTA MARIA VALLEY, CALIF. - VIEWS.
- Santa Maria, Jesus, 1848? - (Box 96)
- Santa Monica Airport (Boxes 246, 286)
- Santa Monica Canyon, California (Box 97)
- Santa Monica Mountains Conservancy (Box 273)
- Santa Monica Mountains National Recreation Area (California) (Box 189)
- Santa Monica Municipal Bus Lines (Boxes 223, 273)
  Box 223 - 3 folders.
- Santa Monica Municipal Bus Lines (Big Blue Bus) (Box 286)
- Santa Monica, California (Boxes 97, 190, 197, 251, 273, 286)
- Santa Monica, California - Business cards, promotional material, etc. (Box 246)
- Santa Monica, California - Description and Travel (Box 273)
- Santa Monica, California - Highways Performance Space (Box 286)
- Santa Monica, California - Hotels, taverns, etc. (Boxes 212, 214, 223, 286)
- Santa Monica, California - Politics and government (Box 97)
- Santa Monica, California - Public Library (Boxes 97, 286)
- Santa Monica, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Boxes 196, 246)
- Santa Monica, California - Santa Monica College (Boxes 186, 246)
- Santa Paula, California (Box 189)
- Santa Rosa, California (Boxes 96, 273)
- Santa Ynez Inn. Pacific Palisades, California (Box 96)
- Santa Ynez Valley (Boxes 96, 287)
- Saratoga, California (Box 274)
- Sargent, Edwin W., 1848 - (Box 96)
  1. SARGENT, EDWIN W., 1848 - - PORTRAIT.
- Saroyan, William, 1908 -. (Box 96)
- Sartori, Joseph Francis, 1858 - 1946 (Box 98)
- Satellite Television (Box 274)
- Savings and loan associations - California - Los Angeles (Box 98)
- Sawtelle, California (Box 274)
- Scherer, James Augustus Brown, 1870 - 1944 (Box 98)
- Schindler, R.M. (Rudolph M.), 1887-1953 (Box 246)
- Schmidt, A.H.R. (Box 98)
  1. SCHMIDT, A.H.R. - PORTRAIT
- Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874 - 1951 (Box 98)
- Schumacher, Frank G. (Box 98)
  1. PHOTOGRAPHERS
- Schwannecke, Henry, 1866? - 1941 (Box 98)
- Scientology (Boxes 246, 251, 274)
- Scott, Walter, 1872 - 1954 (Box 98)
- Screen Writers' Guild (Box 98)
- Scribes. Los Angeles, California. (Box 98)
  The Scribes. 1. LOS ANGELES, CALIF. - HISTORY.
- Seaside resorts - California (Box 98)
- Sebastopol, California (Sonoma County) (Box 98)
- Secunda, Arthur, 1927 - (Box 98)
- See's Candies. Long Beach, California (Box 246)
- Self Realization Fellowship. Pacific Palisades, California (Boxes 192, 287)
- Selig, William N., 1864? - 1948 (Box 98)
- Selma, California (Box 192)
- Senior citizens - California (Box 192)
- Sentinel (The). Los Angeles. (Box 199)
  Former entry: Negroes - California
  - Sentinel 50: commemorative 50th anniversary publication., April 14, 1983.; Item No. 1 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    Fiftieth anniversary issue of the Sentinel, the Los Angeles weekly newspaper devoted to the African American community.
- Sepulveda, Don Jose (Box 98)
- Sequoia National Park. California (Box 98)
  1. GENERAL GRANT NATIONAL PARK. 2. PARKS - CALIFORNIA
- Serra, Junipero, Father, 1713 - 1784 (Box 98)
- Serrano Indians (Box 223)
- Service industries - Los Angeles County (Box 98)
  - Learn Spanish!., undated.; Item No. 2 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Handbill from the Progressive System School, located on 311 Spring Street, advertising language classes in social and business Spanish.
- Severance Club. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
- Sex-oriented businesses (Box 274)
- Shannon, William Edward, 1823 - 1850 (Box 99)
- Shasta County, California (Box 99)
- Shasta River, California (Box 99)
- Shasta, California (Box 99)
- Shasta, Mt. (Box 99)
- Shatto family (Box 99)
- Shaw, David Augustus, 1826 -1915 (Box 99)
- Sheets, Millard, 1907 - (Box 192)
- Sherman Oaks, California (Box 223)
- Sherman Oaks, California. Sherman Theatre. (Box 99)
- Sherman, California (West Hollywood, California) - Directories (Box 212)
  X West Hollywood, Calif.
- Sherman, Moses Hazeltine, 1853 - 1932 (Box 99)
- Shields Date Garden. Indio, California (Box 274)
- Shopping malls - California (Box 274)
- Shopping malls - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 196, 246, 274)
- Shopping malls - Northern California (Box 274)
- Shopping malls - Southern California (Boxes 212, 246, 274)
  Box 246 - 2 folders. Box 274 - 2 folders.
- Shopping services - Southern California (Box 196)
- Shoshone, California (Box 249)
- Shoup, Paul, 1874 - 1946 (Box 99)
- Shulman, Julius (Box 249)
- Sierra Club. Angeles Chapter. (Box 249)
- Sierra Madre, California (Boxes 99, 190)
- Sierra Nevada Mountains (Box 99)
- Silicon Valley (Box 249)
- Silva, Carlos Francisco (Box 287)
- Silva, Rafaela (Ruiz), 1836? - 1941 (Box 99)
  X RUIZ, RAFAELA
  - Death claims pioneer at 105., 1941.; Item No. 1 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Small clipping announcing the 1941 death of Mrs. Rafaela Silva, the oldest native-born Santa Barbara resident at the time.
- Simi Valley, California (Boxes 190, 195)
- Simon Wiesenthal Center. Los Angeles, California. (Boxes 212, 287)
- Simpson, O.J., 1947 - (Box 212)
- Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1878 - (Box 136)
  Folder 1 of 2.
- Single Tax League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 99)
- Siskiyou Mountains, California (Box 99)
- Sittell family (Box 99)
- Skirball Cultural Center. Los Angeles, California. (Box 249)
- Skydiving (Box 223)
- Skyforest, California (Box 249)
- Smith College Club of Southern California (Box 99)
- Smith, Clark Ashton, 1893 - 1961 (Box 99)
- Smith, Helen Brady, 1881? - 1941 (Box 99)
- Smith, Paul Jordan, 1885 - (Box 99)
- Smith, Sylvester Clark, 1858 - 1913 (Box 99)
- Smythe, William Ellsworth, 1861 - 1922 (Box 99)
- Snyder, Meredith Pinxton, 1859 - 1937 (Box 99)
- Social Dance (Box 274)
- Social work - California (Box 192)
- Socialist Party - California, Southern (Boxes 99, 197)
- Societies - Los Angeles, California.
  SEE: Los Angeles, Calif. - Clubs
- Society of Architectural Historians. Southern California Chapter. Pasadena, California (Boxes 249, 251)
- Society of California Archivists (Box 180)
- Solano County, California (Box 99)
- Solvang, California (Box 99)
  1. SOLVANG, CALIF. - VIEWS
- Sonoma County, California (Boxes 99, 287)
  1. SONOMA COUNTY, CALIF. - VIEWS
- Sonora, California (Box 223)
- Sontag, Susan (Box 274)
- Sony Pictures Studios. Culver City, California (Box 249)
- South Coast Air Quality Management District. Diamond Bar, California (Box 223)
- South Pasadena Ostrich Farm (Box 100)
- South Pasadena, California (Boxes 100, 275)
- Southern California - Maps (Box 275)
- Southern California Acclimatizing Association (Box 100)
- Southern California Conservatory of Music (Box 100)
- Southern California Council for UNESCO. Los Angeles. (Box 100)
  1. UNTIED NATIONS EDUCATIONAL, SCIENTIFIC AND CULTURAL ORGANIZATION. LOS ANGELES.
- Southern California Edison Co. (Box 192)
- Southern California Gas Co. (Boxes 212, 249)
- Southern California horticulture (Box 100)
- Southern California Jewish Historical Society (Box 100)
- Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research. Los Angeles. (Box 186)
- Southern California Loan Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 100)
- Southern California Local History Council (Box 100)
- Southern California Rapid Transit District (Box 275)
- Southwest Museum. Los Angeles, California. (Box 249)
- Souvenir of the American Bankers Association Convention, Oct 4, 1926 (Box 263)
  Illustrated guide to homes of noted cinema stars in Hollywood and Beverly Hills
- Spadra, California (Los Angeles County) (Box 100)
- Spaulding, William Andrew, 1852 - 1941 (Box 100)
- Special Olympics Southern California (Box 287)
- Spence, Robert Earl, 1896 - 1974 (Box 100)
- Spiritual healing (Box 192)
- Spiritual life - societies, etc. - directories (Box 189)
- Spiritualism (Box 212)
- Sport fishing (Box 287)
- Sports (Box 180)
- Sports camps - Los Angeles (Box 212)
- St. Denis, Ruth, 1880 - (Box 90)
- St. Helena, California (Box 90)
- Stahlberg, Frederick (Box 100)
  1. STAHLBERG, FERDERICK - PORTRAIT.
- Stanford University (Boxes 100, 197)
- Stanford, Jane Elizabeth (Lathrop). 1828 - 1905 (Box 100)
- Stanford, Leland, 1824 - 1893 (Box 100)
- Stanislaus County, California (Box 100)
- Stanislaus River (Box 100)
  1. STANISLAUS RIVER - VIEWS.
- Stanton, California (Box 275)
- Star Wars (Motion picture) (Box 249)
- Star, Inc. (Box 249)
- Stark, Abigail, 1859 - 1939 (Box 100)
  1. LOS ANGELES - STREETS - FLOWER STREET.
- Steinbeck, John, 1902 - 1968 (Box 101)
- Steinborn, Gary (Box 101)
  1. CERAMICS.
- Steinitz, Kate Trauman, 1893 - (Box 101)
- Stephens, William Dennison, 1859 - 1944 (Box 101)
- Sterling, George, 1869 - 1926 (Box 101)
  1. STERLING, GEORGE, 1869 - 1926 - PORTRAIT.
- Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850 - 1894 (Boxes 101, 203)
  Box 101 - 2 folders.
- Stimson family (Box 101)
- Stockton, California (Boxes 101, 275)
- Stoddard, Charles Warren, 1843 - 1909 (Box 101)
- Stoermer, Grace L. (Box 101)
- Stone, Irving, 1903 - (Box 102)
- Stoneman, George, 1822 - 1894 (Box 102)
- Stores, retail - California - Los Angeles (Box 249)
- Storytelling (Box 223)
- Strauss, Levi (Box 102)
  1. STRAUSS, LEVI - PORTRAIT.
- Strikes, lockouts - Los Angeles (Box 102)
- Studio for Southern California History. Los Angeles, California. (Box 287)
- Sturges, Preston (Box 189)
- Subculture - California - Los Angeles (Box 275)
- Subway Rapid Transit Association. Los Angeles. (Box 212)
  SEE ALSO: Los Angeles, Calif. - subways
- Subways
  SEE: Subway Rapid Transit Association. Los Angeles.
- Sulphur Mountain Springs. Ventura County, California (Box 102)
- Summerland, California (Box 249)
- Summers, Mrs. Emma A., 1858? - 1941 (Box 102)
- Sumo Wrestling (Box 275)
- Sun City, California (Box 223)
- Sunkist (Box 225)
  SEE ALSO: California Fruit Growers Exchange
- Sunland, California (Box 226)
- Sunset Club. Los Angeles. (Box 102)
- Supermarkets (Boxes 213, 218, 248, 287)
  Box 218 - 2 folders. Box 248 - 5 folders.
  Box 213 is an oversize box.
- Sutro, Adolph Heinrich Joseph, 1830 - 1898 (Box 102)
- Sutter County, California (Box 287)
- Sutter, John Augustus, 1803 - 1880 (Box 102)
- Sutter's Fort State Historical Monument. Sacramento, California (Box 102)
- Suydam, Nellie, 1877 - 1946 (Box 102)
  1. GLENDORA, CALIF.
- Swift, John Franklin, 1829 - 1891 (Box 102)
  1. SWIFT, JOHN FRANKLIN, 1829 - 1891 - PORTRAIT.
- Swift, Lewis, 1820 - 1913 (Box 102)
- Synanon Foundation. Santa Monica, California (Box 102)
- Syndicalism (Box 195)
- Taft, Fred H., 1867? - 1942 (Box 181)
- Tahoe, Lake (Boxes 181, 287)
- Tahoe, Lake - Skiing (Box 224)
- Tamalpais, Mount - California (Boxes 181, 203)
  1. MOUNT TAMALPAIS AND MUIR WOODS RAILWAY. 2. MUIR WOODS NATIONAL MONUMENT, CALIF.
  3. TAMALPAIS, MOUNT - VIEWS. Also oversize.
- Tarzana, California (Box 103)
- Tattoos (Box 275)
- Taxis (Box 249)
- Taylor, Bayard, 1825 - 1878 (Box 103)
- Taylor, Edward Robeson, 1838 -1923 (Box 103)
- Tea (Box 275)
- Tecopa Hot Springs, California (Box 275)
- Tehachapi, California (Box 275)
- Tehama County, California (Box 103)
- Tejon Pass, California (Box 103)
  1. TEJON PASS, CALIF. - VIEWS.
- Telephone - history (Box 103)
- Telephone companies (Box 249)
- Telephone companies - California (Boxes 212, 287)
- Television (Box 103)
- Television - Los Angeles (Box 103)
- Television shows - Los Angeles (Box 103)
- Temecula, California (Boxes 249, 287)
- Temescal Valley, California (Riverside County) (Box 103)
- Temple (Francis Pliny Fisk) family (Box 103)
  1. TEMPLE, ANITA (DAVOUST), 1867? -1942.
- Tennis (Box 275)
- Theater - California - Los Angeles (Boxes 182, 212, 287)
  (Original folder missing 11/92). New folder started 11/92.
- Theater - California - Pasadena (Box 189)
- Theater - California, Southern (Box 224)
- Theodore Payne Foundation. Sun Valley, California (Boxes 189, 287)
- Theosophical Fraternity in Health and Healing (Box 103)
- Thomas, Evalyn Ann, - 1950 (Box 103)
- Thompson, Joseph (Box 103)
- Thousand Oaks, California (Boxes 189, 275)
- Thrower, Norman Joseph Williams (Box 103)
- Tiburon, California (Box 275)
- Ticket brokerage (Box 287)
- Tinseltown Tattler. West Hollywood, California (Box 249)
- Title Insurance and Trust Co. Los Angeles. (Box 103)
  1. TITLE INSURANCE AND TRUST CO., LOS ANGELES - VIEWS.
- Toastmasters International. Mission Viejo, California (Box 224)
- Tomatoes - California (Box 287)
- Topanga Canyon, California (Los Angeles County) (Box 103)
  1. TOPANGA CANYON CANYON, LOS ANGELES COUNTY, CALIF. - VIEWS.
- Toreador (Box 103)
  The Toreador. Issued monthly by the University Club of Los Angeles.
- Torrance, California (Boxes 103, 275)
- Tourist trade - California, Southern (Box 181)
- Town Hall. Los Angeles, California. (Box 181)
- Towne, A.N., 1829 - (Box 181)
  1. TOWNE, A.N., 1829 - - PORTRAIT.